Joby

Cheruvazhaplavil

Sr.Customer Service Executive

ABOUT ME

A teneris impende laborem (Apply yourself to hard work from an early age). A Family man and strong believer on working hard. I have more than 5 years of experience in customer service industry (Call, chats and email) along with business client handling. Always open to new learnings and experience to upskill and adapt.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Contrado Imaging India Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

Customer Service Representative (Blend Process Call, chats emails)

Feb. 2020 - PRESENT

- Build positive client relations and offer assistance to business and retails client understanding the site
 designs layout and help with creating customized designs and production real time for cater to their
 purchase requirements.
- offer assistance to new and upcoming business, sellers, creatives to set up an online store front
 and understand site layout and design features along with offering basic knowledge on SEO
 channels and online promotions.
- Mitigating between internal team and clients regarding product, design aesthetic and on time job completion to maintain highest customer service standards.
- Review and contribution on new company articles, product launches, site functionality, bugs, promotions and upselling.
- Preparing and maintaining regular reports and data on pending orders, production delay and urgent order fulfilment.
- Communicating with clients via call, chat or email for any upcoming promotions, order delays.
- Liaison between client and delivery partners to ensure a smooth end to end process on order fulfilment and delivery.

Vodafone Shared Services Pvt. Ltd, Ahmedabad— Sr. Associate Dec, 2017 - Jan, 2019

- Offered real time assistance to customer based in UK for questions related to billing, active plans and telecom features, such as bundles, available upgrades, contract terms, charges etc.
- Helped with detailed billing breakdown, extra recurring charges and removal of any non-standard or unwanted feature on their active bundle.
- Offered real time assistance to customer based in UK for questions related to billing, active plans and telecom features, such as bundles, available upgrades, contract terms, charges etc.

CONTACT



9714838478



nesbagt@gmail.com



Theoutcasts.in



A 32 Ram Tirth Apartment Naroda Gam Ahmedabad 382330

Expertise Skills

Research & strategy

Good communication and interpersonal skills

Escalation handling

Verbal and written communication

Training and Development

Escalation Handling

Business and Process Development

Soft Skills

Strengths and intrests

Strength

- · Flexibility and adaptability
- Team building and
- Time Management
- Discipline
- Learning Agility
- · Positive Approach
- Respectfulness

Intrest

- Travel and Gourmet
- Passive Blogging
- Designing, art, re-creation
- Reading
- Gaming

Projects

- Worked with Aussiz Education for Student Education visa and awareness Fair 2019
- Completed onsite project as a 3rd Party vendor for Cadila AHU Pipelining and process plant development2012
- Part of 4 men team to introduce 6
 a-side soccer tournament 1st time
 in Gujarat

- Helped with detailed billing breakdown, extra recurring charges and removal of any nonstandard or unwanted feature on their active bundle.
- Handling customer escalations over the chat and call (if required) to ensure time actions and assistance to maintain a positive customer experience with services rendered.
- Mentored and helped new team members for smooth onboarding process to ensure that they
 are ready with all tools and knowledges required for business.
- Active Contribution to adapt and help implement new process changes, features and help all team members adapt to the same.
- Maintaining daily scores, and reporting to Tl's on team performance and ensuring daily required scores and targets and met without hurdles.
- Up-selling services and helping customer reach upgrade channels effectively for plan /service upgrades.

Motiff India Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad— Jr. Advisor Dec, 2016 - Dec, 2017

- Offering assistance via chat and emails for questions on purchase, sales promotions discounts, limited time offers.
- Help buyers with bidding process, sales and after sales assistance. Providing detailed guidance to buyers and mitigating between buyers and sellers in case of issues with online purchase.
- Mitigating and an acting liaison between buyer and sellers to help complete the purchase and
 offering assistance to buyers and help them understand buyer protection program to help build
 confidence with purchase.
- Handling escalations and helping buyers under buyer protection act online and helping them
 with cancellation and refund in case of any issue with purchase.
- Assisting new team mates with questions and queries and heling with smooth onboarding process. Help learn the process and internal jargon, along with understanding the criticality of their job to ensure business values are inculcated
- Identify false advertisement/scammer and immediate removal of any such advertisement to
 ensure buyers remain protected and also to ensure company branding is not being impacted.
- Review, maintain and contribute to internal knowledge base and ensure that all teams are being
 updated on new updates and changes regularly during team huddles.

Email (bi-lingual)

- Offer Russian customer assistance via emails related to purchase and sales of goods.
- Help local Russian customer with returns and refund on goods purchased. Checking their custom policies for returns and mitigating between buyers and sellers accordable reach an amicable resolution.
- Identifying and testing new translation tools to minimize translation error for smooth communication.
- Preparing, creating and editing new email draft for personal and internal team use after testing
 it on various translation tools to ensure 0 error draft.

National Moulds and Dye, Ahmedabad

Management/CNC-Operator Jan 2010- 2015

- Providing and taking quotations offline/online.
- Client Relations
- · Overseeing and maintaining inventory.
- Mitigation with teams and organization.
- Handling purchase and sales/inventory management.
- Overseeing smooth functioning of the plant and ensuring completion of projects in timely manner
- Designing tool, dyes, molds
- Sample creation and Testing
- Maintaining Payroll data (Excel)
- Maintaining Employee Account and salary
- Data and record safe keeping
- •

Education

St. Xavier's Loyola Hall, Ahmedabad — H.S.C. (Commerce)

K.P.E.S Commerce Collage Bhavnagar

Final year Pending

- Helped with detailed billing breakdown, extra recurring charges and removal of any nonstandard or unwanted feature on their active bundle.
- Handling customer escalations over the chat and call (if required) to ensure time actions and assistance to maintain a positive customer experience with services rendered.
- Mentored and helped new team members for smooth onboarding process to ensure that they
 are ready with all tools and knowledges required for business.
- Active Contribution to adapt and help implement new process changes, features and help all team members adapt to the same.
- Maintaining daily scores, and reporting to Tl's on team performance and ensuring daily required scores and targets and met without hurdles.
- Up-selling services and helping customer reach upgrade channels effectively for plan /service upgrades.

Motiff India Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad— Jr. Advisor Dec, 2016 - Dec, 2017

- Offering assistance via chat and emails for questions on purchase, sales promotions discounts, limited time offers.
- Help buyers with bidding process, sales and after sales assistance. Providing detailed guidance to buyers and mitigating between buyers and sellers in case of issues with online purchase.
- Mitigating and an acting liaison between buyer and sellers to help complete the purchase and
 offering assistance to buyers and help them understand buyer protection program to help build
 confidence with purchase.
- Handling escalations and helping buyers under buyer protection act online and helping them with cancellation and refund in case of any issue with purchase.
- Assisting new team mates with questions and queries and heling with smooth onboarding
 process. Help learn the process and internal jargon, along with understanding the criticality of
 their job to ensure business values are inculcated
- Identify false advertisement/scammer and immediate removal of any such advertisement to
 ensure buyers remain protected and also to ensure company branding is not being impacted.
- Review, maintain and contribute to internal knowledge base and ensure that all teams are being
 updated on new updates and changes regularly during team huddles.

Email (bi-lingual)

- Offer Russian customer assistance via emails related to purchase and sales of goods.
- Help local Russian customer with returns and refund on goods purchased. Checking their custom policies for returns and mitigating between buyers and sellers accordable reach an amicable resolution.
- Identifying and testing new translation tools to minimize translation error for smooth communication.
- Preparing, creating and editing new email draft for personal and internal team use after testing
 it on various translation tools to ensure 0 error draft.

National Moulds and Dye, Ahmedabad

Management/CNC-Operator **Jan 2010- 2015**

- Providing and taking quotations offline/online.
- Client Relations
- · Overseeing and maintaining inventory.
- Mitigation with teams and organization.
- Handling purchase and sales/inventory management.
- Overseeing smooth functioning of the plant and ensuring completion of projects in timely manner
- Designing tool, dyes, molds
- · Sample creation and Testing
- Maintaining Payroll data (Excel)
- Maintaining Employee Account and salary
- Data and record safe keeping

.